It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on TV
But where are those
good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man
who positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry
He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy!
Hey, you guys ever check Zillow?
Joe, why don't you shut the...
Tell me more about this silly word.
It's this website, Zillow.com.
You plug in your address,
and it gives you an estimate
of what your house is worth.
But they call it a Zestimate,
because of the "Z" in "Zillow."
How do they...
I just don't have that creative bone.
Wow, my house is way up
from when I bought it.
- Mine's up, too.
- What the hell?
Mine's way below
what you guys's are worth.
Wait, this-this can't be right.
It says... it says
my house is a murder house.
What, like-like someone
was killed there?
Yeah, it says... it says, in the '60s,
some woman named Doris
Billingsly died in my house.
Probably some naggy bitch, right?
- Joseph!
- You know, they say
when someone dies violently like that,
- their spirit can linger.
- What do you mean?
Ea I'm saying you might have
a g-g-g-g-g...
disembodied spirit in your house!
Wow, this is so cool.
Have you ever witnessed
anything strange there?
Actually, now that you mention it...
Good news! The biopsy was negative.
Did you hear something?
Hi, Chris.
Oh, hey, Kristen. What's up?
Not much. I wanted to know
if you're gonna go
to the dance on Friday.
Nah, probably not.
Oh, that's too bad.
I was thinking maybe
you and I could go together.
Oh, that's sweet, but, like I said,
I-I don't think I'm gonna go.
Well, if you change your mind...
I said no!
Okay. Geez.
Bye, Chris.
Uh, Chris, that very attractive girl
just asked you out, and you said no.
Well, sorry, Brian,
she just doesn't do it for me.
I'm hungry.
I might grab a bite to eat.
We all just ate, right?
What's wrong with that kid?
Why wouldn't he go out with that girl?
Who knows? Maybe he's gay.
What? No.
Well, you never know. I say we find out.
You think he could be?
Hey, I've been right
about these things before.
Remember what I said in 2009?
- Bruce Jenner is a man.
- No, Brian.
That's what the press would
have you believe, but he's not.
Bruce Jenner is a woman.
An elegant, beautiful Dutch woman.
Okay, guys, now, the murder took
place down here in the basement,
so it's probably our best shot
at finding something.
I do feel a presence in the air.
Only Lucifer would reveal
himself to you, adulterer.
Well, now, I have to warn you fellas...
The only spirits I'm used to
chasing are whiskey and tequila.
That's so Joe!
Wow, what's going on down here?
Trying something new for Joe.
And we're looking for ghosts.
We're like the male version
of the female Ghostbusters.
Peter, there's no such thing as ghosts.
I don't know why you guys
listen to a word he says.
That's so Lois.
All right, we ready?
Wow, it is creepy.
So, what do we do?
Just follow my lead.
Are there any spirits present
that would like to communicate with us?
What the hell was that?
I got scared and tried to run
through the wall,
leaving a hole shaped like me.
Yeah, can't do that in a basement, bud.
All right, fellas, I just
finished up an EVP session.
Let's see if we picked anything up.
What's EVP?
Electronic voice phenomenon.
Oftentimes, the human ear
can't pick up paranormal sounds,
but electronic recording devices can.
Mm. That right?
Is this whole thing just you
beefing into the microphone?
Yeah.
Dad, they did this bit
in the lady Ghostbusters.
Did you hear something?
Stewie, I'm telling you,
there's no way Chris is gay.
Oh, why, because he never hit on you?
God, the ego.
Hey, Chris. What's up?
Just relaxing, listening to some
of Charles Manson's music.
What's up with you guys?
Actually, Brian and I
are taking a survey,
and we wanted to see
if you had a few minutes.
- Sure. Go ahead.
- Okay, question one.
What night are the Tony Awards?
Tony Danza has awards?
Name an appropriate price
to pay for jeans.
Um, five dollars?
What year did Bette Midler release
"You've Got to Have Friends"?
Oh, 1972.
And it was fabulous!
Chris, are you gay?
What? No, I'm not gay.
Well, then why didn't you go out
with that girl?
Why would I?
I have everything I need in
that department on my computer.
You have 28 windows of porn
playing simultaneously?
Sometimes I pretend I'm
at the security desk at the mall
and everyone at the mall
is banging each other.
Chris, don't you see?
You're so desensitized by all this porn,
you're-you're not
even interested in actual girls.
Wh-What are you doing?
I'm taking this, and we are
gonna help you start thinking
about sex like a normal teenager.
A-All right, I'll give it a shot.
But it's not gonna be easy.
I had a hell of a time
getting off sugar.
Chris, can you pass the syrup?
Oh, you want the syrup, old man?!
Yeah!
Yeah, nice attached head, Meg.
Body, throw potatoes.
Winner declared!
Okay, guys, now, I thought
we could try to find the ghost
by doing the movie Flatliners.
- I've never seen it.
- Me, neither.
Oh, my God. All right, we are
stopping everything right now
and watching Flatliners.
I'm all right...
I'm glad we switched to Caddyshack.
You know what, Peter, I think
I've had enough ghost hunting.
- I'm done, too.
- Yeah, I'm out.
Wait, why you leaving?
Because all you do is screw around.
We've been down here for hours,
and we haven't found a thing.
Well, maybe that's because you
guys don't know the first thing
about catching ghosts.
You know what, Lois was right.
We should just never listen to you.
Come on, guys.
I think you're all just scared.
Oh, yeah? Let's see who's scared.
What are you doing?
Turn that light back on.
Have a good night, Peter.
Quagmire. Help!
Someone help me!
Hey! Open this door!
Don't leave me alone with the ghost!
Help! Help!
Help!
What the hell?
Peter, are you okay?
I was... down here all night.
So dark.
Oh, my God. Peter, your hair.
It turned white.
What?
Well, I'm a fat dad with white hair now.
Time to become an issue
at Hooters after 9:00 p.m.
Hey, Ashley. Ashley.
Ashley.
I know... I know what car is your car.
So, how'd you get white hair again?
He was scared of a ghost.
Yes, I remember hearing
about this in med school.
Or was it a Scooby-Doo?
You think it's gonna stay, Dr. Hartman?
No, it's gonna be "Dr. Ramirez" now.
I'm taking my husband's name.
I'm talking about Peter's hair.
Oh, I'm sorry. Wedding on the brain.
But, uh, as for the white hair,
I'm afraid it's permanent.
Hi, sweetie.
We've discussed this.
No to the mole.
Chocolate is for cake, not chicken.
Oh, come on.
He's crying.
What do I do now?
I mean, should I dye it back?
I don't know why you'd ask me that.
I mean, I-I don't know anything
about that.
How does one even go about
dyeing one's hair?
I've never heard of anything so crazy.
Let me get that for you, Doctor.
What? Oh, no, I'm-I'm not a...
Morning, Doctor.
Wow, Peter,
they all think you're a doctor
because of your white hair.
I have to say, it does make you
look more distinguished.
Really? Huh.
Well, maybe this will be
a good thing after all.
Like a garbageman with no nose.
Well, this is the best job in the world!
Rotting meat?
What does that smell like?
Oh, look, receipts.
I'll steal this person's identity.
From now on, I'm Robert Dibadeaux.
So long, stinkies!
Not that I would know.
All right, Chris,
it's gonna take a few steps
to get you off hard-core porn.
Now, the first step is soft-core porn,
where nothing really happens.
Oh, wow, she is just riding
that guy's belly button.
Yep, that's all we had.
And you could watch this at any time?
No, just Friday at 11:45 p.m.
And it was free?
No, $45 a month.
Well, what was playing
the other 200 hours per week?
Uh, mostly D.A.R.Y.L.
The movie D.A.R.Y.L.
Was it any good?
It was okay.
Grandpa, what are you doing here?
Using the bathroom.
Where do you keep the nets
that you put on the bottom
of guys' balls
to stop 'em from dunking in the water?
- What?
- What do you mean, "What?"
Where do you keep the nets
that you put on the bottom
of guys' balls
to stop them from dunking in the water?
Oh, there's my silver fox.
What are you doing out here?
Well, now that I've got white hair,
I fix my car in slow motion
in an ad for a supplemental
blood thinner.
I took Zanbrex
for over 15 years,
till I learned the benefits
of once-daily Sanguelto,
a latest-generation blood thinner.
When I'm at a multiracial
picnic for some reason,
the last thing I want to do
is have a stroke.
And thanks to once-daily Sanguelto,
I can eat potato salad
with chuckling strangers
with the confidence of someone who knows
he's 12% less likely
to suffer a stroke recurrence.
Thanks to Sanguelto, I can snuggle
with my age-appropriate wife
on a blanket
underneath
non-holiday-related fireworks.
I left her for six weeks back in 2009,
only to realize I was already too old
to bed the type of women
that would make
such a separation worth it.
So, here we are, grinding it out
till onef us has that second stroke
that you don't come back from.
Thank you, Sanguelto.
What's all this?
Well, a lot of kids'
first foray into sex
is looking at someone else's porn stash.
So, here's a stack
of water-stained Playboys
that I found in a locker
at the town pool bathroom.
Okay, now we're talking.
Wait. I'm clicking on this thumbnail,
but the video isn't opening.
No, that's a still image.
See, you look at them,
and then your brain sort of
creates a scene for you.
I don't know. I think maybe
we should try something else.
I think you should give it a shot.
I think we should all go investigate
the still-unsolved murder
of Doris Billingsly,
who never did anything
but overcook one dinner
in March of 1962.
All right, I got next round.
- Hey, Tom, you okay?
- She left me.
Another sign from the universe
that I'll never find love.
Hey, come on, pal. There's
plenty of fish in the sea.
Wow.
You're right. There are.
Say, you've got a way about you,
a certain... trustworthy quality.
You know, we've got an opening
at the station for a senior analyst.
I think your white hair
would be perfect for it.
Wow. Really? What do I do?
You just act like everyone else
is an idiot and shout over them.
- That way, you can...
- Shut up! I get it!
Terrific. Hey, why don't you come down
to the station tomorrow and...?
- I know where you work!
- Again, terrific.
Wow, this is awesome.
I haven't been on TV since
I had IBS on The Bachelorette.
Derek, I had such a magical weekend.
You are truly one of a kind.
And that's why I've decided to...
Excuse me. Uh, do-do you know
if I'm gonna get a rose?
We're getting to that, Peter.
Derek, that's why I've decided
to give you this rose.
Evan, getting to see
your softer side was truly...
Excuse me.
I hate to be a bother, but do you...
do you know if I'll be receiving a rose?
Because if there's, uh, further delay,
I believe something's gonna happen
that will put me
out of contention for a rose.
And that thing just happened.
Farewell, and thank you
for feeding me champagne
and shrimp all day.
Reporting live from Quahog Prison,
I'm Joe Horrigan, Channel Five News.
Thanks, Joe.
Great reporting, terrible eyes.
Switching gears now, I'd like to talk
about the crime situation
here in Quahog.
Joining me now is white-haired
contributor Peter Griffin.
Peter, what are you hearing
about crime in Quahog?
Uh... you know, not much.
Not much? Excuse us for one moment.
- What are you doing?!
- What?
I don't know anything about crime.
So? People want to know that
bad stuff's going on out there.
That's why they watch the news.
- You want me to make stuff up?
- I don't know.
I thought you had white hair.
- You're right, I do.
- Of course you do.
Now, you were talking about crime?
Crime is way up, and you know why?
'Cause of immigrants.
I say, as Americans,
we should all take a pledge
to kick 'em out.
Only pledge I stand for is Lemon Pledge.
Peter Griffin, white hair, very
credible, thank you so much.
Coming up, lost dog comes home...
one piece at a time.
Peter, that was amazing.
I'm the news director
here at Channel Five.
How would you like to do
what you just did every night?
Wipe a bloody booger under the desk?
No, I'm asking you to join us full-time
to be our permanent senior analyst.
Would you excuse me
while I step into another room
and celebrate like a girl in a
Rom-com who just got good news?
Aah! The Sanguelto!
My blood's thinner than water!
If taking Sanguelto,
please refrain
from dancing like in a Rom-com,
as nosebleeds may be permanent.
And remember, most drugs
are prescribed to you
because a hot girl
with a rolling suitcase
gave your doctor a free pen.
Peter, what the hell
do you think you're doing?
Who says you can just make
things up and call them facts?
Tom Tucker did. He kissed me.
You have a responsibility
as a member of the press
to report the news accurately.
You can't just say crazy things
that aren't in any way true.
Yeah, leave that to the yahoos in D.C.
- Did that get a "That's So Joe"?
- No!
Okay, well, what are the rules on that?
We're still working that out.
Well, let me know
when you decide on the rules.
I'm really excited
about working on this.
With you guys.
Chris, welcome
to the lingerie department.
What are we doing here?
When I was young, seeing
these half-naked mannequins
was all I needed to get me going.
What's the endgame here...
Him walking around Macy's with a chub?
No, we've got
to reset his arousal meter.
He needs to be able
to use his imagination again.
Any of these mannequins
doing anything for you, Chris?
Uh, I don't know.
I guess the one
without a head is pretty cool.
All right, that's... that's something.
And that bin of chopped-up ones
over there... that could be okay.
'Specially the one
that looks kind of afraid.
There you go. Look at you.
Sounds like someone is ready
for that date.
Do you gentlemen need any help?
No, thank you, dear.
We're just trying
to get my brother to full mast.
We want to welcome back our new
permanent senior analyst,
Peter Griffin and his white hair.
What's the latest on crime in Quahog?
- Tom, crime is up.
- Wow. How high?
- All the way to the top.
- Whoa. The top.
Has it ever been all the way
to the top before, Peter?
Never. In fact, we had to raise the top.
So, the new top is even higher
than the old top?
Yes, the old top is now the middle.
And The Middle is a show
that was inexplicably on ABC
for a very long time.
How many seasons?
It might be, like, 11.
I'm not even kidding.
Peter Griffin, white hair, very
credible, thank you so much.
Coming up, we'll tell you where to look
when a person has a birthmark
on their face.
So, Chris, have you weaned
yourself off of Internet porn?
Wait. I thought the whole point
was to not wean myself off.
No, Chris, I mean,
have you stopped...? Never mind.
- You ready for your date?
- You bet I am!
Hi, Chris.
Hi, Kristen.
Ready to see a Marvel movie,
'cause I chose?
Sure. And for sure this is a real date,
and me and the popular kids
aren't gonna thrill-kill you tonight.
I think Chris is gonna be just fine.
Which is more than I can say
for our pizza.
Oh, man.
Well, I hope you're happy.
You're telling lies on the news
just to boost your own ego.
It's pronounced "Eggo," Lois,
and I will thank you to leggo of mine.
Peter, fake news is a real problem
in this country right now,
and I really don't want
my husband contributing to it.
Maybe you're right.
It doesn't feel good lying all the time.
I guess I just like all the attention
that came along with having white hair.
Well, I don't think that's
the kind of attention you want.
And it's certainly not
the kind of attention
I want for our family.
You know what?
If it means that much to you,
I'll tell Tom
that I won't do it anymore.
- Really?
- Really.
Oh, Peter, that makes me so happy.
Hello? Donald Trump?!
You saw me on the news?
You want me to be your press
secretary in the next episode?
Why, sure, I'd love to!
We'll get started drawing it right away.
Lois, pack your bags.
We're joining the Trump Administration.
Just what Washington needs, huh?
Another talking head.
Oh, man.
Next week on Family Guy...
Hey, Dad, I want you
to meet my new friend, Meg.
Pleased to meet you, Meg.
You have a beautiful rack.
Oh, thanks.
I was talking to my daughter.
And now, please welcome
Mr. Bruce Jenner.
Just wanted to remind you fellas
what you're all fighting for.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.tv